Guide to the William Martin Religious Right research collection, 1975-2000 MS 537
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series I: Videos, interviews and transcripts (Boxes 1-76), 1995-1996
  - 009.043.2 Episode 6 Selects: Christian Coalition Proposes New Contract (1995); Abortion in Kansas (1991); Abortion Murder (1993); Operation Rescue/ Abortion Protests (1991); Mike Fremd Spot (1993); The White House (1990) - (Beta, DVD), March 11, 1996 (Box 10, Folder -)
  - 009.044.2 Episode 6 Selects: Operation Rescue/ Abortion Protests (1991); Operation Rescue Rally (1991) - (Beta, DVD), March 11, 1996 (Box 10, Folder -)
  - 009.045.2 Operation Rescue/Abortion Protests (1991); Detroit Feed (1992); President Bush Vacationing (1991) - (Beta, DVD), March 11, 1996 (Box 10, Folder -)
  - 009.046.2 "Man of the People" Reagan Campaign 1980; Carter 5th Graders, March 19, 1996; Beta (Box 10, Folder -)
  - 009.047.1 Gays in the Military (1993); Dole Reaction (1992); Lake County Schools, March 20, 1996; Beta (Box 10, Folder -)
  - 009.048.2 Democracy (1993); Bush-Quayle Campaign (1988); 1992 Republican National Convention, March 28, 1996; Beta (Box 10, Folder -)
  - 009.049.2 1992 Republican Convention in Houston; Nightline on Abortion (1991); Oliver North/ God and the GOP (1993); Bush with Religious Broadcasters (1988), March 29, 1996; Beta (Box 10, Folder -)
  - 009.050.2 Bush with Religious Broadcasters (1988); Abortion (1988); 1992 Conventions, March 28, 1996; Beta (Box 10, Folder -)
  - 009.051.2 Episode 5, April 5, 1996; Beta (Box 10, Folder -)
  - 009.052.2 Episode 5, April 5, 1996; Beta (Box 10, Folder -)
  - 009.052.2B Campaign 1988; Iowa Caucus Coverage; Nuttle Interview - Selects Only, Undated; Beta (Box 10, Folder -)
  - 009.053.2 Reagan at 1992 Convention, April 3, 1996; Beta (Box 10, Folder -)
  - 009.054.2 Kids With AIDS (Ep. 5 - 1995), April 11, 1996; Beta (Box 10, Folder -)
  - 009.055.2 Episode 6: George Bush Inauguration (1989); Campaign 1988 Super Tuesday; Clinics (1993), April 17, 1996; Beta (Box 10, Folder -)
  - 009.056.2 Kanawha Coal Miners Strike (September 19, 1974), April 17, 1996; Beta (Box 10, Folder -)
  - 010.001.5 Lewanne Jones: Christian Footage, May 16, 1995; VHS (Box 11, Folder -)
  - 010.002.5 Elvis Presley Footage, Undated; VHS (Box 11, Folder -)
  - 010.002.5 Episode 1: Elvis Presley, Undated; Beta (Box 11, Folder -)
  - 011.001.4A "With God On Our Side" Reel #1(Part 1 of 2) Zero 1960; J. Birch Society; Film II; The New Cinema, June 21, 1995; Beta (Box 11, Folder -)
  - 011.001.4B "With God On Our Side" Reel #1(Part 2 of 2) Zero 1960; J. Birch Society; Film II; The New Cinema, June 21, 1995; Beta (Box 11, Folder -)
  - 011.002.4A "With God On Our Side" Reel #2 (Part 1 of 2) Before the Harvest; In a Quiet Place, June 21, 1995; Beta (Box 11, Folder -)
  - 011.002.4B "With God On Our Side" Reel #2 (Part 2 of 2) Before the Harvest; In a Quiet Place, June 21, 1995; Beta (Box 11, Folder -)
  - 011.003.4 "With God On Our Side" Reel #3: Parent to Child About Sex; The War We Are In, Pt. II, June 21, 1995; Beta (Box 11, Folder -)
  - 011.004.4 "With God On Our Side" Reel #4: Sex in the Sixties; Something to Think About; Mike and Ann, June 21, 1995; Beta (Box 11, Folder -)
  - 011.005.4 "With God On Our Side" Reel #5: The World of Billy Graham, June 21, 1995; Beta (Box 11, Folder -)
  - 012.007.5 Making Sense of the Sixties (Little Richard, MLK, Anti-war Protests, etc.), Undated; Beta (Box 11, Folder -)
  - 012.011.5 Frontline #601 "Praise the Lord", Undated; Beta (Box 11, Folder -)
  - 013.001.5 Ted Koppel Report: Part 1 (May 12, 1988), May 12, 1988; Beta (Box 11, Folder -)
  - 013.001.5 Ted Koppel Report: Part 1 (May 12, 1988), May 12, 1988; VHS (Box 11, Folder -)
  - 013.002.5 Ted Koppel Report: Part 2 (May 12, 1988), May 12, 1988; VHS (Box 11, Folder -)
  - 013.003.5 Nightline (March 3, 1987) Copy 1 of 2, March 3, 1987; Beta (Box 11, Folder -)
  - 013.003.5 Nightline (March 3, 1987) Copy 2 of 2, March 3, 1987; Beta (Box 11, Folder -)
  - 013.004.5 Nightline - April 27, 1987, April 27, 1987; VHS (Box 12, Folder -)
  - 013.005.5 Nightline - May 27, 1987 (Part I), May 27, 1987; VHS (Box 12, Folder -)
  - 013.006.5 Nightline - May 27, 1987 (Part II), May 27, 1987; VHS (Box 12, Folder -)
  - 013.007.5 NBC News - March 25 and 26, 1987; ABC News - March 25, 1987, March 25 and 26, 1987; VHS (Box 12, Folder -)
  - 013.007.5 NBC News - March 25 and 26, 1987; ABC News - March 25, 1987, March 25 and 26, 1987; Beta (Box 12, Folder -)
  - 013.008.5 People for the American Way "Life and Liberty for All Who Believe", Undated; Beta (Box 12, Folder -)
  - 013.008.5 People for the American Way "Life and Liberty for All Who Believe", Undated; VHS (Box 12, Folder -)
  - 013.009.5 People for the American Way "Censorship in Our Schools: Hawkins County, Tennessee, November 1987; VHS (Box 12, Folder -)
  - 013.010.5 People for the American Way "A Battle for Public Education", Undated; VHS (Box 12, Folder -)
  - 013.011.5 People for the American Way "The Religious Right: In Their Own Words", Undated; VHS (Box 12, Folder -)
  - 013.012.5 Republican National Convention (August 23, 1984) - Robison, Falwell, Reagan; Falwell's School Prayer Special (Copy 1 of 2), May 9, 1982; Beta (Box 12, Folder -)
  - 013.012.5 Republican National Convention (August 23, 1984) - Robison, Falwell, Reagan; Falwell's School Prayer Special (Copy 2 of 2), May 9, 1982; VHS (Box 12, Folder -)
  - 013.012.5 Republican National Convention (August 23, 1984) - Robison, Falwell, Reagan; Falwell's School Prayer Special, May 9, 1982; VHS (Box 12, Folder -)
  - 013.013.5 Robertson on CBN Expansion; 700 Club, September 27, 1982 (Box 12, Folder -)
  - 013.014.5 People for the American Way "America's Cultural Civil War", Undated; Beta (Box 12, Folder -)
  - 013.015.5 The People for the Story, May 27, 1988; Beta (Box 12, Folder -)
  - 013.016.5 VISTA "A Battle for Public Education" People for the American Way, Undated; VHS (Box 12, Folder -)
  - 013.017.5 The New World Order/ CEE Debate Part I, Undated; VHS (Box 12, Folder -)
  - 013.019.5 Falwell; Wake Up America; Attack on the Family; Meet the Press: Up to the Minute - Abortion; Nightline - Targeted Senators (VHS, DVD), Undated (Box 12, Folder -)
  - 013.019.5 Jerry Falwell at Family Forum, Undated; Beta (Box 12, Folder -)
  - 013.020.2 Selects Dubbed from VHS 013.020.5 - Rally for Life 1981, Undated; Beta (Box 12, Folder -)
  - 013.020.5 Rally For Life 1981; Frost Special; World In Action (VHS), Undated (Box 12, Folder -)
  - 013.020.5 Rally For Life 1981; Frost Special; World In Action (Beta, DVD), Undated (Box 12, Folder -)
  - 013.020.3 to 013.043.5 (Box 13, Folder -)
  - 013.044.5 to 013.057.1 (Box 14, Folder -)
  - 013.059.1 to 018.001.5 (Box 15, Folder -)
  - 018.002.1 to 023.014.1 (Box 16, Folder -)
  - 024.001.5 to 030.009.5 (Box 17, Folder -)
  - 030.010.5 to 030.028.5 (Box 18, Folder -)
  - 031.007.5 to 031.021.5 (Box 19, Folder -)
  - 032.001.5 to 034.002.5 (Box 20, Folder -)
  - 034.002.5 to 034.012 (Box 21, Folder -)
  - 038.005.2 to 046.001.2 (Box 22, Folder -)
  - 047.001.1 to 055.001.5 (Box 23, Folder -)
  - 055.002.5 to 057.010.5 (Box 24, Folder -)
  - 057.011.5 to 071.005.1 (Box 25, Folder -)
  - 073.001.2 to 083.004.5 (Box 26, Folder -)
  - 083.006.5 to 087.025.5 (Box 27, Folder -)
  - 087.026.5 to 088.002.1 (Box 28, Folder -)
  - 088.003.2 to 092.001.4 (Box 29, Folder -)
  - 092.013.1 to 101.003.2 (Box 30, Folder -)
  - 101.005.5 to 111.005.2 (Box 31, Folder -)
  - 112.001.4 to 119.001.2 (Box 32, Folder -)
  - 120.001.1 to 138.002.5 (Box 33, Folder -)
  - 999.001.1 to 999.010.1 (Box 34, Folder -)
    Scope and Contents note
    Interview tapes beginning with numbers 999 generally do have transcripts. See boxes 73-76 for the names of persons interviewed and their tape numbers.
  - 999.011.2 to 999.021.1 (Box 35, Folder -)
  - 999.022.2 to 999.031 (Box 36, Folder -)
  - 999.032 to 999.042.2 (Box 37, Folder -)
  - 999.043.2 to 999.053 (Box 38, Folder -)
  - 999.054 to 999.064.2 (Box 39, Folder -)
  - 999.065.1 to 999.075.2 (Box 40, Folder -)
  - 999.076.1 to 999.086.2 (Box 41, Folder -)
  - 999.087.1 to 999.097.2 (Box 42, Folder -)
  - 999.098.1 to 999.109.2 (Box 43, Folder -)
  - 999.110.1 to 999.120.2 (Box 44, Folder -)
  - 999.121.1 to 999.131.2 (Box 45, Folder -)
  - 999.132.1 to 999.142.2 (Box 46, Folder -)
  - 999.143.1 to 999.153.2 (Box 47, Folder -)
  - 999.154.1 to 999.164.2 (Box 48, Folder -)
  - 999.165.1 to 999.175.2 (Box 49, Folder -)
  - 999.176 to 999.186.2 (Box 50, Folder -)
  - 999.187.1 to 999.197.2 (Box 51, Folder -)
  - 999.198.1 to 999.208.2 (Box 52, Folder -)
  - 999.209.1 to 999.219.2 (Box 53, Folder -)
  - 999.220.1 to 999.230.2 (Box 54, Folder -)
  - 999.231.1 to 999.241.2 (Box 55, Folder -)
  - 999.242.1 to 999.252.2 (Box 56, Folder -)
  - 999.253.1 to 999.263.2 (Box 57, Folder -)
  - 999.264.1 to 999.274.2 (Box 58, Folder -)
  - 999.275.1 to 999.285.2 (Box 59, Folder -)
  - 999.286.1 to 999.296.2 (Box 60, Folder -)
  - 999.297.1 to 999.307.2 (Box 61, Folder -)
  - 999.308.1 to 999.317.2 (Box 62, Folder -)
  - 999.318.1 to 999.328.2 (Box 63, Folder -)
  - 999.329.1 to 999.338.2 (Box 64, Folder -)
  - 999.339.1 to 999.349.2 (Box 65, Folder -)
  - 999.350.1 to 999.360.2 (Box 66, Folder -)
  - 999.361.1 to 999.371.2 (Box 67, Folder -)
  - 999.372.1 to 999.382.2 (Box 68, Folder -)
  - 999.383.1 to 999.393.2 (Box 69, Folder -)
  - 999.394 to 999.395 (Box 70, Folder -)
  - unlabeled video cassettes (Box 71, Folder -)
  - audio cassettes (Box 72, Folder -)
  - Transcripts
    - Robert Maddox 999-004-2 to 999-006-2, Interview: Box 34 (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - Pat Robertson 999-007 to 999-008, Interview: Box 34 (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - Carl Henry 999-009 to 999-014, Interview: Box 34-35 (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - Beverly and Tim LeHaye 999-016 to 999-019, Interview: Box 35 (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - Doctor Dunn 999-023 to 999-024 and 999-134, Interview: Box 36, 46 (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - Coach McCartney 999-027, Interview: Box 36 (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - Regier 999-039 to 999-042, Interview: Box 37 (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - Sharon Overcast 999-043 to 999-046, Interview: Box 38 (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - Jody Powell 999-047 to 999-049, Interview: Box 38 (Box 73, Folder 9)
    - Morton Blackwell 999-049 to 999-053, Interview: Box 38 (Box 73, Folder 10)
    - Dr. Virgil Wood 999-054 to 999-056, Interview: Box 39 (Box 73, Folder 11)
    - Rebecca Owen 999-057 to 999-059 (2 folders), Interview: Box 39 (Box 73, Folder 12)
    - Rebecca Owen 999-057 (2 of 2), Interview: Box 39 (Box 73, Folder 13)
    - Connie Marshner 999-060 to 999-063, Interview: Box 39 (Box 73, Folder 14)
    - Stuart Eisenstdt 999-064 to 999-066, Interview: Box 39-40 (Box 73, Folder 15)
    - A. Pierre Guillermin 999-067 to 999-069, Interview: Box 40 (Box 73, Folder 16)
    - O.C. Thaxton 999-070 to 999-072, Interview: Box 40 (Box 73, Folder 17)
    - Elmer Towns 999-073 to 999-075, Interview: Box 40 (Box 73, Folder 18)
    - Jerry Falwell 999-076 to 999-080 (1 of 2), Interview: Box 41 (Box 73, Folder 19)
    - Jerry Falwell 999-076 to 999-080, (2 of 2) Interview: Box 41 (Box 73, Folder 20)
    - M.W. Thornhill 999-081 to 999-082, Interview: Box 41 (Box 73, Folder 21)
    - Haywood Robinson 999-083 to 999-086, Interview: Box 41 (Box 73, Folder 22)
    - Bill Godsey 999-088 to 999-091, Interview, Box: 42 (Box 73, Folder 23)
    - Nancey Godsey and Melody Albert 999-092 to 999-096 (1 of 2), Interview: Box 42 (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - Nancy Godsey and Melody Albert 999-092 to 999-096 (2 of 2), Interview: Box 42 (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - Charlotte Gaylor 999-097 to 999-099, Interview: Box 42-43 (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - Barbara Shannon 999-100 to 999-101, Interview: Box 43 (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - Peter Guilquist 999-102 to 999-104, Interview: Box 43 (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - E.V. (Ed) Hill 999-105 to 999-108, Interview: Box 43 (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - James Townsend 999-109 to 999-112, Interview: Box 43-44 (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - Eleanor Howe 999-113 to 999-114, Interview: Box 44 (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - Sally Williams 999-115 to 999-116, Interview: Box 44 (Box 74, Folder 9)
    - Jon Braun 999-117 to 999-120, Interview: Box 44 (Box 74, Folder 10)
    - James Moffett 999-121 to 999-123, Interview: Box 45 (Box 74, Folder 11)
    - Cynthia Karraker 999-124 to 999-125, Interview: Box 45 (Box 74, Folder 12)
    - Cal Thomas 999-127 to 999-130, Interview: Box 45 (Box 74, Folder 13)
    - Os Guinness 999-131 to 999-134, Interview: Box 45-46 (Box 74, Folder 14)
    - Bill Billings 999-135 to 999-138, Interview: Box 46 (Box 74, Folder 15)
    - Michael Deaver 999-139 to 999-140, Interview: Box 46 (Box 74, Folder 16)
    - Whittlesey 999-141 to 999-145, Interview: Box 46-47 (Box 74, Folder 17)
    - Udo Middlemann 999-146 to 999-149, Interview: Box 47 (Box 74, Folder 18)
    - Kenneth Briggs 999-150 to 999-153, Interview: Box 47 (Box 74, Folder 19)
    - Harold Leif 999-154 to 999-155, Interview: Box 48 (Box 74, Folder 20)
    - Rev. Lewis 999-156 to 999-158, Interview Box: 48 (Box 74, Folder 21)
    - Emmett Shafer 999-163 to 999-164; Kinsolving 999-165, Interview: Box 48-49 (Box 74, Folder 22)
    - Mike Edds 999-171 to 999-174, Interview: Box 49 (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - Elmer Fike 999-175 to 999-176, Interview: Box 49-50 (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - Phyllis Schlafly 999-182 to 999-186 (1 of 2), Interview: Box 50 (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - Phyllis Schlafly 999-182 to 999-186 (2 of 2), Interview: Box 50 (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - Guy Rogers 999-187 to 999-192 (1 of 2), Interview: Box 51 (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - Guy Rogers 999-187 to 999-192 (2 of 2) Interview: Box 51 (Box 75, Folder 6)
    - Ralph Reed 999-193 to 999-195, Interview: Box 51 (Box 75, Folder 7)
    - John Conlan 999-196 to 999-200 (1 of 2), Interview: Box 51-52 (Box 75, Folder 8)
    - John Conlan 999-196 to 999-200 (2 of 2) Interview: Box 51-52 (Box 75, Folder 9)
    - Sen. Mark Hatfield 999-203 to 999-204, Interview: Box 52 (Box 75, Folder 10)
    - James Robison 999-205 to 999-208, Interview: Box 52 (Box 75, Folder 11)
    - Dick Weinhold 999-209 to 999-213, Interview: Box 53 (Box 75, Folder 12)
    - Sam Clark 999-224 to 999-226, Interview: Box 54 (Box 75, Folder 13)
    - Harold Brown 999-227 to 999-229, Interview: Box 54 (Box 75, Folder 14)
    - Evelyn Davis and Mary Robinson 999-230 to 999-233, Interview: Box 54-55 (Box 75, Folder 15)
    - Edith Schaeffer 999-234 to 999-238, Interview: Box 55 (Box 75, Folder 16)
    - Grover Norquist 999-239 to 999-240, Interview: Box 55 (Box 75, Folder 17)
    - Mark Nuttle 999-241 to 999-243, Interview: Box 55-56 (Box 75, Folder 18)
    - Billy James Hargis 999-244 to 999-248, Interview: Box 56 (Box 75, Folder 19)
    - Jimmy Allen 999-249 to 999-251, Interview: Box 56 (Box 75, Folder 20)
    - Martin Mawyer 999-252 to 999-256, Interview: Box 56-57 (Box 75, Folder 21)
    - Haywood Robinson, Jr. 999-261 to 999-265, Interview: Box 57-58 (Box 75, Folder 22)
    - David Cunningham 999-267 to 999-269, Interview: Box 58 (Box 75, Folder 23)
    - C. Everett Koop 999-270 to 999-273, Interview: Box 58 (Box 75, Folder 24)
    - Bobbie Kilberg 999-274 to 999-279, Interview: Box 58-59 (Box 75, Folder 25)
    - Carl Anderson 999-280 to 999-283, Interview: Box 59 (Box 75, Folder 26)
    - Ira Manhoff 999-281 to 999-282, Interview: Box 59 (Box 75, Folder 27)
    - Leigh Ann Metzger 999-284 to 999-288, Interview: Box 59-60 (Box 75, Folder 28)
    - Randall Terry 999-289 to 999-294, Interview: Box 60 (Box 75, Folder 29)
    - Kathy Potera 999-296 to 999-298, Interview: Box 60-61 (Box 75, Folder 30)
    - Ed Dobson 999-299 to 999-303, Interview: Box 61 (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - James Muffet 999-304 to 999-307, Interview: Box 61 (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - Lorinda Wortz 999-308 to 999-310, Interview: Box 62 (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - Peter Secchia 999-312 to 999-315, Interview: Box 62, 1995-12-16 (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - Claudia Ramsey 999-316 to 999-317, Interview: Box 62 (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - Claudia Ramsey and Pat Hart 999-317 to 999-321, Interview: Box 62-63 (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - Pat Hart 999-321 to 999-322, Interview: Box 63 (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - John Dowless 999-324 to 999-325, Interview: Box 63 (Box 76, Folder 8)
    - Dave Walters 999-326 to 999-328, Interview: Box 63 (Box 76, Folder 9)
    - D. Dunlap 999-329 to 999-330, Interview: Box 64 (Box 76, Folder 10)
    - Carolyn Sundseth 999-331 to 999-334, Interview: Box 64 (Box 76, Folder 11)
    - John Gilman 999-335 to 999-339, Interview: Box 64-65 (Box 76, Folder 12)
    - John Woodbridge 999-340 to 999-344, Interview: Box 65 (Box 76, Folder 13)
    - Pat Robertson 2nd interview 999-345 to 999-346, Interview: Box 65 (Box 76, Folder 14)
    - Phil Campbell 999-347 to 999-351, Interview: Box 65-66 (Box 76, Folder 15)
    - Bill McCartney 999-358 to 999-359, Interview: Box 66 (Box 76, Folder 16)
    - E.J. Dionne 999-360 to 999-361, Interview: Box 66-67 (Box 76, Folder 17)
    - John Carr 999-363 to 999-366, Interview: Box 67 (Box 76, Folder 18)
    - Connie Snap 999-366 to 999-368, Interview: Box 67 (Box 76, Folder 19)
    - Marlene Elwell 999-369 to 999-373, Interview: Box 67-68 (Box 76, Folder 20)
    - Michael Horton 999-383 to 999-387, Interview: Box 69 (Box 76, Folder 21)
    - Harvey Cox 999-388 to 999-390, Interview: Box 69 (Box 76, Folder 22)
    - Gen. J. Curry 999-391 to 999-393, Interview: Box 69 (Box 76, Folder 23)
    - Charles Colson, Interview: Box 71 (Box 76, Folder 24)
    - Kathryn Long, Interview: Box 71 (Box 76, Folder 25)
    - Ken Swanson, Interview: Box 71 (Box 76, Folder 26)
    - Paul Weyrich, Interview: Box 71 (Box 76, Folder 27)
    - Mel White, Interview: Box 71 (Box 76, Folder 28)
    - Televangelist and News Indexes (Box 76, Folder 29)
    - Unidentified Transcript Fragments (Box 76, Folder 30)
- Series II: Subject files, 1978-1996 (Boxes 77-91)
  - File Index (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Subseries A: Alphabetical subject files
    - Abortion, Suicide, Euthanasia (Box 77, Folder 2)
      - Abortion - Articles and Info (Box 77, Folder 2, Subfolder 1)
      - Randell Terry (Box 77, Folder 2, Subfolder 2)
      - Abortion - Operation Rescue (Box 77, Folder 2, Subfolder 3)
      - Abortion, Suicide, Euthanasia (Box 77, Folder 2, Subfolder 4)
    - AIDS (1 of 3) (Box 77, Folder 3)
      - AIDS-General (Box 77, Folder 3, Subfolder 1)
      - Jimmy Allen Story (Box 77, Folder 3, Subfolder 2)
        General
        Scans of "Burden of a Secret" pages 148-248 along with part of an article in Classic Confrontation titled "What Happened to the Southern Baptist Convention?"
      - Jimmy Allen Press Conference, 1980 (Box 77, Folder 3, Subfolder 3)
        Three pages from Spiritual Politics
      - SBC/Jimmy Allen (Box 77, Folder 3, Subfolder 4)
        Southern Baptist Convention President. A number of news articles about Jimmy Allen's grandsons who were infected by H.I.V. through a blood transfusion to her grandmother. There were also transcripts of CBS, NBC etc.
    - AIDS (2 of 3), 1987-01-01-1987-05-31 (Box 77, Folder 4)
      A number of news articles about AIDS between the dates above. Also some academic articles about the AIDS crisis.
    - AIDS (3 of 3) (Box 77, Folder 5)
      - Koop/AIDS Research/Books (Box 77, Folder 5, Subfolder 1)
        Research for a book by C. Everett Koop, a former American medical officer, generally about the evangelical response to the AIDS crisis. This includes transcripts of interviews, handwritten notes, and one newspaper, among other items.
      - Confronting AIDS/Koop (Box 77, Folder 5, Subfolder 2)
        This folder includes news articles some academic journals and highlights. There was also a reaction to Koop's views on AIDS. Koop's timeline, articles from Christianity Today, WSJ, and Washington Times. There was also a list of secondary sources about Koop, and more generalized book planning.
      - AIDS and The Church (Box 77, Folder 5, Subfolder 3)
        Stories of AIDS among ministers, and a magazine (Body Positive) issue from June, 1995.
    - Amendment 2 (Box 77, Folder 6)
      The passage of Amendment 2 in Colorado that legalized discrimination against LGBTQ+ individuals. Transcript from the PBS show in Bill Moyers' Journal (1993). There was also a Political Science abstract "No Special Rights": The Thinking Behind Colorado's Amendment #2 Strategy. Included a Bill McCartney interview.
    - Americans for Constitutional Freedom (Box 77, Folder 7)
      A booklet entitled "Sense and Censorship The Vanity of Bonfires: Resource Materials on Sexually Explicit Material, Violent Material and Censorship: Research and Public Policy Implications" by Marcia Pally.
    - American Family Association (Box 77, Folder 8)
      A New York Times newspaper advertisment paid for by the American Family Association, this also included the October, 1993 edition of the AFA journal. There were also a number of other AFA articles and journals.
    - American Jewish Committee (Box 77, Folder 9)
      This includes a religious liberty sabbath project including a series of interreligious sermons, a couple of booklets. This booklet included some opposition towards prayer in school.
    - Americans United for Separation of Church (Box 77, Folder 10)
      Anti-Religious Right organization with flyers and other mattrials. Educational materials also included articles distributed by the AUSCS, including 7 Church and State publications 1988 and 1995.
    - Anderson, Carl (Box 77, Folder 11)
      Informationa about Carl Anderson a member of the White House Staff and of the Knights of Columbus along with former legislative aide to Jesse Helms. There was also an interview for the Koop project and some news transcripts as well.
    - Anti-Defamation League (Box 77, Folder 12)
      There were a lot of materials from the Anti-Defemation League including a Amicus brief, litigation materials, and other various pamphlets and news.
    - Athletes in Action (Box 77, Folder 13)
      iInformation and emails from the Athletes in Action organization including a newspaper and a newsletter entitled "A Strategic Game Plan to Impact the World Through the Influence of Sports."
    - Bakker, Jim and Tammy (Box 77, Folder 14)
      Tammy Bakker and her attempt to come back to public life alongside her husband Jim Bakker who was a televangelist convicted of fraud/conspiracy. In addition, reflections by Jim and Tammy in the New Yorker.
    - Barton, David (Box 77, Folder 15)
      Historical understanding of no separation between church and state. Barton also started the organization Wallbuilders which had the goal of enhancing the religious right.
    - Bibliography (Box 77, Folder 16)
      This had a series of articles and books that listed secondary sources, bibliofile intelligent catalog, and lists of the secondary sources.
    - Blackwell, Morton (Box 77, Folder 17)
      Blackwell was a conservative special assistant to the Reagan administration. This included interview transcripts, his CV, literature from the Leadership Institute about conservative organization, and a paper by Blackwell about the consolidation of the New Majority Coalition.
    - Book Coverage (Box 77, Folder 18)
      - Redeeming America (Box 17, Folder 18, Subfolder 1)
        "Redeeming America" included notes from Jerret Engle on a book by Michael Lienesch
      - Fall From Grace (Box 17, Folder 18, Subfolder 2)
        "Fall From Grace: The Failed Crusade of the Christian Right" by Michael D'Antonio. This book was detached and cynical about the religious right. Notes the increase of conservative christianity at the expense of moderate Protestantism.
    - Bork, Robert (Box 77, Folder 19)
      - Bork, Robert (Articles) (Box 77, Folder 19, Subfolder 1)
        A number of news articles about the contested Supreme Court confirmation of Robert Bork